<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">LibrarySpace</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_group">GroupActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_individual">IndividualActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_multimedia">MultimediaActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_conditions">ConditionsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_booking">BookingActivity</string>
    <string name="conditions_group_bodyText">Group Study Rooms may be reserved by GROUPS OF 3 OR MORE. Individuals wanting to study alone should reserve an Individual Study Carrel instead. Groups of 2 people should use one of the first-come, first-served study rooms.
\n\nUsers must be CSUSB students, faculty, or staff.

\n\nIf a group has not occupied the room within 10 minutes of their start time, the reservation is forfeited, and other groups may use the room. A single individual cannot "hold" a study room for a group arriving later.

\n\nA group with a reserved room time has priority over a group occupying that room without a reservation. We recommend that you bring your final confirmation email as proof in case of a dispute.

\n\nReservations are limited to two hours per group, per day, with a total limit of four hours per week.

\n\nReservations may be made up to a week in advance.

\n\nBy continuing, you agree to these conditions of use. </string>

    <string name="conditions_individual_bodyText">Study carrels are for use by ONE PERSON! Groups should book a Group Study Room instead, or use one of the first-come, first-served group study rooms.

\n\nUsers must be CSUSB students, faculty, or staff.

\n\nIf you have not occupied the carrel within 10 minutes of your start time, your reservation is forfeited, and others may use the carrel.

\n\nAnyone with a reserved room time has priority over someone occupying that room without a reservation. We recommend that you bring your reservation email as proof in case of a dispute.

\n\nReservations are limited to two hours per day, per person.

\n\nReservations may be made up to a week in advance, with a total limit of six hours per week.

\n\nBy continuing, you agree to these conditions of use. </string>
    <string name="conditions_multimedia_bodyText">The Multimedia Collaboration rooms are NOT intended for group study. They can comfortably seat from 1 to 4 people in front of the computer workstation. If you need a regular study room for your group, book a group study room instead, or use one of the first-come, first-served study rooms.

\n\nUsers must be CSUSB students, faculty, or staff.

\n\nIf you have not occupied the room within 10 minutes of your start time, your reservation is forfeited, and others may use the room.

\n\nAnyone with a reserved room time has priority over someone occupying that room without a reservation. We recommend that you bring your reservation email as proof in case of a dispute.

\n\nReservations are limited to two hours per user/group, per day, with a total limit of four hours per week.

\n\nReservations may be made up to a week in advance.

\n\nBy continuing, you agree to these conditions of use. </string>

</resources>
